<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Peter Maguire</title><link>https://petermaguire.xyz/</link><description>Recent content on Peter Maguire</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><copyright>&amp;copy; 2023 Peter Maguire</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:13:27 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://petermaguire.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Zhiyun Weebil-S BLE Protocol</title><link>https://petermaguire.xyz/posts/zhiyun-weebil-s-ble-protocol/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:13:27 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://petermaguire.xyz/posts/zhiyun-weebil-s-ble-protocol/</guid><description>Note: Source code for an example implementation is available here
Introduction The Weebill-S is a mirrorless/DSLR camera gimbal made by Zhyiun that retails for around £389. It can be controlled either from the device itself or with a companion app on your phone via bluetooth. I purchased mine from ebay at a very reasonable price but with a defect, the onboard controls don&amp;rsquo;t work so you are required to use the app to control it.</description></item><item><title>BbyStealer Analysis</title><link>https://petermaguire.xyz/posts/bbystealer-analysis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 22:10:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://petermaguire.xyz/posts/bbystealer-analysis/</guid><description>BbyStealer is one of the most prevalent information stealing malware that exists on Discord today. It has been around since approximately December 2021 and has evolved several times. This article focuses on the version from December 2022, but may make references to older versions where appropriate.
Spread BbyStealer is sold as Malware as a Service, so the spread varies depending on the individual malicious actor (called &amp;ldquo;operators&amp;rdquo; for the rest of this article).</description></item><item><title>Employment History</title><link>https://petermaguire.xyz/work/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 15:05:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://petermaguire.xyz/work/</guid><description>More information is available on my LinkedIn.
MachineMax Backend Developer June 2023 - Present
Writing Go microservices Ably Realtime SDK Developer II January 2022 - June 2023
Worked on Ably&amp;rsquo;s public SDKs, primarily JS based. Sportech Software Developer August 2019 - December 2021
Worked primarily in Go, with some React and PHP. Responsible for owning and developing microservices. Managed the Google Cloud instance with Terraform. Managed the company GitLab instance, including managing the CI/CD.</description></item><item><title>Epsilon Stealer Malware Analysis</title><link>https://petermaguire.xyz/posts/epsilon-stealer-analysis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 17:47:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://petermaguire.xyz/posts/epsilon-stealer-analysis/</guid><description>Spread Epsilon generally spreads via the game tester scam. The victim is prompted to try out a game from an itch.io link. The download generally contains an archive, usually RAR, which has a password. The password will be given to the victim via Discord, this is to try and evade automated scanning/execution by anyone other than the victim.
An example DM a victim would receive Infection Once the victim has downloaded the archive and extracted it, they will be faced with a Unity game.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://petermaguire.xyz/projects/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 17:28:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://petermaguire.xyz/projects/</guid><description>OcelotBOT 2013 - Present
OcelotBOT is a multipurpose Discord bot aimed at servers with small groups of people.
Written in JS, with some auxiliary services written in Go. Currently used by ~60,000 servers. ~1,000 Daily Active Users. Hosted on Docker Swarm. Ethan 2017 - Present
Ethan is a Discord currency bot for RP servers.
Based on the framework built for OcelotBOT. Used in ~600 servers. Hosted on Docker Swarm.</description></item></channel></rss>